(Penny:)Forget it.
I'll pay you $40.
Saturday, 9:00 a.m.
Bring cash.
(Howard:)Raj, I have amazing news!
(Sheldon:)What?
(Howard:)I just got offered
a fellowship
(Howard:)at the Weitzmann
Institute in Israel.
(Raj:)Dude, that's incredible!
I know.
(Howard:)The only thing is, I'm
gonna be gone for two years.
(Raj:)Aw, I'm gonna miss you.
(Raj:)Are you going with him?
(Bernadette:)I have to stay
here for school.
(Howard:)That's what we're here
to talk to you about.
(Sheldon:)You see,
Bernadette has needs.
(Raj:)What kind of needs?
(Howard:)Sexual needs.
(Bernadette:)Most of them regular,
(Bernadette:)some of them
kind of messed up.
(Howard:)So, while I'm gone,
(Howard:)you're going
to have to satisfy her.
(Bernadette:)What do you say?
(Raj:)I say okey-dokey.